Finding Aid for the Music Center records LSC.3261
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 6: Dorothy Chandler Pavilion files, 1858-2017
  - Center Dance Association ephemera, undated (Box 1540, Folder 1-4)
    This box contains two pairs of men's boots, one Dance at the Music Center pin, and one signed Center Dance Association t-shirt.
  - Center Dance Association ephemera, undated (Box 1541, Folder 1-4)
    This box contains one pair of red velvet men's shoes, one pair of powder blue satin pointe shoes signed by Leslie Carothers, one pair of DeAnn Duteil's red satin pointe shoes from Les Patineurs, and one pair of navy blue pointe shoes.
  - Academy Awards files, 1969-1970 (Box 1542, Folder 1-15)
    This box contains an Oscars biographical file, a portrait collection of Academy Awards winners from 1928-1961, and 40 Years with Oscar at the Academy Awards booklet with a foreword by Bette Davis.
  - Academy Awards files, 1970-1972 (Box 1543, Folder 1-14)
  - Academy Awards files, 1973-1974 (Box 1544, Folder 1-7)
  - Academy Awards files, 1974-1982 (Box 1545, Folder 1-13)
  - Academy Awards files, 1982-1987 (Box 1546, Folder 1-12)
  - Academy Awards files, 1987-1992 (Box 1547, Folder 1-5)
  - Academy Awards files, 1992-1994 (Box 1548, Folder 1-6)
  - Academy Awards files, 1994 (Box 1549, Folder 1-3)
  - Academy Awards files, 1987, 1996-1999 (Box 1550, Folder 1-6)
    This box contains the book: Oscar Dearest: Six Decades of Scandal, Politics, and Greed Behind Hollywood's Academy Awards. This box also contains two VHSs: Oscars and 71st Annual Academy Awards.
  - Academy Awards files, 1977, 1999, 2005 (Box 1551, Folder 1-3)
    This box contains a VLIFE Oscar Portfolio and a World Marketing Alliance (WMA), Inc. Academy Awards Gala commemoration program. This box also contains one 16mm Sea Trials Harry Watson film.
  - Dorothy Chandler Pavilion window cards, undated (Box 1552, Folder 1)
  - Dorothy Chandler Pavilion window cards, undated (Box 1553, Folder 1)
  - Dorothy Chandler Pavilion posters, undated (Box 1554, Folder 1)
  - Dorothy Chandler Pavilion posters, undated (Box 1555, Folder 1)
  - Dorothy Chandler Pavilion posters, undated (Box 1556, Folder 1)
  - Resolutions, 1969-2003 (Box 1557, Folder 1-13)
  - Dorothy Chandler Pavilion ephemera, 1976-1984 (Box 1558, Folder 1-3)
    This box contains mounted photographs of Bunker Hill before construction of the Dorothy Chandler Pavilion, a color snapshot of the Pavilion, and Charles Pierce paste-ups.
- Series 7: Center Theatre Group files, 1732-2010
  On March 20, 1966, Dorothy Buffum Chandler, president of the Performing Arts Council of the Music Center, announced the Center Theatre Group (CTG) as the resident professional dramatic company of the Music Center. This announcement followed an agreement that the Theatre Group under managing director Gordon Davidson would move from UCLA to the Music Center. The formation of the Theatre Group under the auspices of the University of California Extension grew out of a conference of 100 academics and theater professionals from across the country held at Lake Arrowhead in 1958. The CTG presents performances at the Mark Taper Forum and the Ahmanson Theatre, both of which were dedicated on April 12, 1967. The Mark Taper Forum opened on April 9, 1967 with "The Devils," starring Frank Langella and Ed Flanders. The Ahmanson Theatre opened on September 12, 1967 with "More Stately Mansions" starring Ingrid Bergman, Arthur Hill, and Colleen Dewhurst.
  Sources: "Theater Group Named Resident of Music Center," Los Angeles Times, March 20, 1966, Mark Taper Forum and Ahmanson Theatre dedication week files, Box 1,623, Music Center records (Collection 3261). UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles. The Music Center Fact Sheet, August 1, 1990.
  The Center Theatre Group files range in date from 1732-2010 and contain Mark Taper Forum programs, season files, season binders, season photographs, and season index cards; Ahmanson Theatre season index cards, season files, photograph index cards, photographs, negatives, slides, window cards, and press files; Ahmanson Theatre at the UCLA James A. Doolittle Theater window cards; Walter Douglas scrapbooks; Mark Taper Forum renovation brochures, agreement, book, and correspondence, pins, reports, and photographs; Mark Taper Forum ephemera, window cards, and architectural blueprints; Mark Taper Forum and Ahmanson Theatre dedication week files; Center Theatre Group audio and audiovisual materials; Kenn Randall early LA theater survey, prompt books, theatre programs, and photographs; Raymond F. Barnes theatre history index cards, LA, NY, and Chicago Legit records, LA vaudeville records, LA theatre programs, Biltmore Theatre programs, Pasadena Playhouse programs, Shrine Auditorium programs, Greek Theatre programs and reviews, Huntington Hartford Theatre programs and reviews, theatre playbill scrapbooks, photographs, and posters; George Zoritch Playbill magazines, photographs, correspondence, programs, and posters; Olga Rosenthal correspondence and New York City Opera photographs; Leiland A. Irish Overture magazines, sheet music, and LA theatre history data; Charles Coburn drama publications and sheet music; and music manuscripts.
  - Mark Taper Forum bound programs, 1967-1970 (Box 1,559, Folder 1-4)
  - Mark Taper Forum bound programs, 1971-1973 (Box 1,560, Folder 1-3)
  - Mark Taper Forum bound programs, 1974-1976 (Box 1,561, Folder 1-2)
  - Mark Taper Forum bound programs, 1976-1979 (Box 1,562, Folder 1-3)
  - Mark Taper Forum bound programs, 1979-1982 (Box 1,563, Folder 1-2)
  - Mark Taper Forum bound programs, 1982-1984 (Box 1,564, Folder 1-2)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1967-1983 (Box 1,565, Folder 1-9)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1967-1969 (Box 1,566, Folder 1-21)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1969-1971 (Box 1,567, Folder 1-20)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1971-1973 (Box 1,568, Folder 1-16)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1973-1975 (Box 1,569, Folder 1-13)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1974-1976 (Box 1,570, Folder 1-14)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1976-1979 (Box 1,571, Folder 1-12)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1978-1980 (Box 1,572, Folder 1-15)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1980-1982 (Box 1,573, Folder 1-17)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1982-1983 (Box 1,574, Folder 1-13)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1983-1985 (Box 1,575, Folder 1-15)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1984-1986 (Box 1,576, Folder 1-14)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1986-1988 (Box 1,577, Folder 1-16)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1987-1989 (Box 1,578, Folder 1-19)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1989-1991 (Box 1,579, Folder 1-20)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1990-1992 (Box 1,580, Folder 1-16)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1991-1992 (Box 1,581, Folder 1-15)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1992-1994 (Box 1,582, Folder 1-14)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1994-1995 (Box 1,583, Folder 1-7)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1994-1996 (Box 1,584, Folder 1-9)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1996-1997 (Box 1,585, Folder 1-8)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1996-1998 (Box 1,586, Folder 1-8)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1997-1999 (Box 1,587, Folder 1-6)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1998-2000 (Box 1,588, Folder 1-7)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 1999-2000 (Box 1,589, Folder 1-10)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 2000-2001 (Box 1,590, Folder 1-8)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 2000-2002 (Box 1,591, Folder 1-7)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 2001-2002 (Box 1,592, Folder 1-21)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 2002-2003 (Box 1,593, Folder 1-11)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 2002-2004 (Box 1,594, Folder 1-13)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 2003-2004 (Box 1,595, Folder 1-15)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 2004-2005 (Box 1,596, Folder 1-9)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 2004-2006 (Box 1,597, Folder 1-8)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 2005-2007 (Box 1,598, Folder 1-9)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 2006-2008 (Box 1,599, Folder 1-6)
  - Mark Taper Forum season files, 2008-2009 (Box 1,600, Folder 1-6)
  - Mark Taper Forum season binders, 1967-1968 (Box 1,601, Folder 1-4)
  - Mark Taper Forum season binders, 1969-1971 (Box 1,602, Folder 1-4)
  - Mark Taper Forum season binders, 1972-1976 (Box 1,603, Folder 1-5)
  - Mark Taper Forum season binders, 1976-1979 (Box 1,604, Folder 1-6)
  - Mark Taper Forum season binders, 1979-1983 (Box 1,605, Folder 1-6)
  - Mark Taper Forum season binders, 1983-1988 (Box 1,606, Folder 1-5)
  - Mark Taper Forum season photographs, 1967-1982 (Box 1,607, Folder 1-120)
  - Mark Taper Forum season photographs, 1982-1995 (Box 1,608, Folder 1-140)
  - Mark Taper Forum season photographs, 1994-1998 (Box 1,609, Folder 1-110)
  - Mark Taper Forum season photographs, 1998-2001 (Box 1,610, Folder 1-85)
  - Mark Taper Forum season photographs, 2000-2006 (Box 1,611, Folder 1-65)
  - Mark Taper Forum season photographs, 1968, 1970 (Box 1,612, Folder 1-57)
  - Mark Taper Forum and Ahmanson Theatre season index cards, A-F, 1967-1993 (Box 1,613, Folder 1)
  - Mark Taper Forum and Ahmanson Theatre season index cards, G-N, 1967-1993 (Box 1,614, Folder 1)
  - Mark Taper Forum and Ahmanson Theatre season index cards, O-Z, 1967-1993 (Box 1,615, Folder 1)
  - Walter Douglas scrapbooks, 1979-1991 (Box 1,616, Folder 1-2)
  - Walter Douglas scrapbook, 1972-2005 (Box 1,617, Folder 1-3)
    This box also contains a framed photograph inscribed to Gordon Jenkins from the company of "The Ring of Steel", a black and white photograph of Gordon Davidson at the Mark Taper Forum, and Mark Taper Forum ephemera including a button and a "Don't Bother Me I Can't Cope" fan.
  - Mark Taper Forum renovation book and brochures, 2006-2008 (Box 1,618, Folder 1-12)
  - Mark Taper Forum renovation agreement and correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 1,619, Folder 1-9)
  - Mark Taper Forum renovation pins, reports, and photographs, 1982-2008 (Box 1,620, Folder 1-11)
    This box also contains a Showtime at the Taper gala desk calendar in honor of Gordon Davidson and Mark Taper and a Mark Taper Forum history draft.
  - Mark Taper Forum ephemera, 1970, 2008 (Box 1,621, Folder 1-2)
    This box contains clippings, a ribbon cutting ceremony invitation list, a Yellow Pages cover, and Act II The Opening of the New Mark Taper Forum tote bags.
  - Mark Taper Forum window cards and architectural blueprints, 1986, 1993, undated (Box 1,622, Folder 2)
    This box also contains a folder of oversize photographs of sketches of Richard Chamberlain, Mary Martin, and Sandy Duncan.
  - Mark Taper Forum and Ahmanson Theatre dedication week files, 1966-1967 (Box 1,623, Folder 1-11)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1967-1988 (Box 1,624, Folder 1-8)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1967-1968 (Box 1,625, Folder 1-7)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1968-1970 (Box 1,626, Folder 1-10)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1970-1972 (Box 1,627, Folder 1-12)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, undated (Box 1,628, Folder 1-12)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1973-1975 (Box 1,629, Folder 1-10)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1975-1977 (Box 1,630, Folder 1-14)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1977-1979 (Box 1,631, Folder 1-14)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1979-1981 (Box 1,632, Folder 1-11)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1981-1983 (Box 1,633, Folder 1-12)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1982-1984 (Box 1,634, Folder 1-12)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1983-1985 (Box 1,635, Folder 1-10)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1985-1986 (Box 1,636, Folder 1-9)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1986-1988 (Box 1,637, Folder 1-15)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1988-1990 (Box 1638, Folder 1-14)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1990-1992 (Box 1,639, Folder 1-11)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1991-1994 (Box 1,640, Folder 1-11)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1989-1994 (Box 1,641, Folder 1-5)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1990-1993 (Box 1,642, Folder 1-8)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1990-1995 (Box 1,643, Folder 1-8)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1994-1995 (Box 1,644, Folder 1-6)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1995-1997 (Box 1,645, Folder 1-7)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1996-1997 (Box 1,646, Folder 1-6)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1997-1998 (Box 1,647, Folder 1-4)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1997-1999 (Box 1,648, Folder 1-6)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1998-2000 (Box 1,649, Folder 1-7)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 1999-2000 (Box 1650, Folder 1-6)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, undated (Box 1,651, Folder 1-4)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 2000-2002 (Box 1,652, Folder 1-4)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 2001-2002 (Box 1,653, Folder 1-3)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 2001-2002 (Box 1,654, Folder 1-4)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 2002-2003 (Box 1,655, Folder 1-8)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 2002-2003 (Box 1,656, Folder 1-8)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 2002-2004 (Box 1,657, Folder 1-9)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 2003-2004 (Box 1,658, Folder 1-9)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 2004-2005 (Box 1,659, Folder 1-9)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 2005-2006 (Box 1,660, Folder 1-8)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 2006-2007 (Box 1,661, Folder 1-7)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, 2007-2008 (Box 1,662, Folder 1-9)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season files, undated (Box 1,663, Folder 1-14)
  - Ahmanson Theatre bound programs, 1967-1971 (Box 1664, Folder 1-5)
  - Ahmanson Theatre bound programs, 1971-1975 (Box 1,665, Folder 1-4)
  - Ahmanson Theatre bound programs, 1975-1977 (Box 1,666, Folder 1-3)
  - Ahmanson Theatre bound programs, 1977-1980 (Box 1,667, Folder 1-3)
  - Ahmanson Theatre bound programs, 1980-1983 (Box 1,668, Folder 1-3)
  - Ahmanson Theatre bound programs, 1983-1986 (Box 1,669, Folder 1-3)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1987 (Box 1,670, Folder 1-12)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1987-1988 (Box 1,671, Folder 1-10)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1988 (Box 1,672, Folder 1-6)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1988 (Box 1,673, Folder 1-8)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1987-1989 (Box 1,674, Folder 1-11)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1988-1989 (Box 1,675, Folder 1-8)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1988 (Box 1,676, Folder 1-11)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1988-1989 (Box 1,677, Folder 1-14)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1989 (Box 1,678, Folder 1-6)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1988-1989 (Box 1,679, Folder 1-13)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1976-1989 (Box 1,680, Folder 1-13)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1989 (Box 1,681, Folder 1-7)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1989-1990 (Box 1,682, Folder 1-7)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1989 (Box 1,683, Folder 1-7)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1989-1990 (Box 1,684, Folder 1-13)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1990 (Box 1,685, Folder 1-12)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1990 (Box 1,686, Folder 1-12)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1989-1991 (Box 1,687, Folder 1-18)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1989-1990 (Box 1,688, Folder 1-16)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1989-1990 (Box 1,689, Folder 1-6)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1990 (Box 1,689, Folder 1-6)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1990-1991 (Box 1,690, Folder 1-13)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 1990-1991 (Box 1,691, Folder 1-10)
  - Ahmanson Theatre press files, 2004-2005 (Box 1,692, Folder 1-7)
  - Ahmanson Theatre photograph index cards, A-L, 1967-1996 (Box 1,693, Folder 1)
    This box contains Absurd Person Singular to Little Family Business.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photograph index cards, L-W, 1967-1996 (Box 1,694, Folder 1)
    This box contains The Little Foxes to The Woman Warrior.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1977-2002 (Box 1,695, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Absurd Person Singular to Another Part of the Forest.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1967-1999 (Box 1,696, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Another Part of the Forest to Beethoven's Tenth.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1982-1998 (Box 1,697, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Beethoven's Tenth to Broadway Bound.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1968-2002 (Box 1,698, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Broadway Bound to The Car Man.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1968-1998 (Box 1,699, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Carousel to Chicago.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1972-2001 (Box 1,700, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains The Cocktail Hour to Crucifer of Blood.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1970-2001 (Box 1,701, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Crucifer of Blood to Detective Story.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1968-1994 (Box 1,702, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Detective Story to Fool Moon.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1970-1999 (Box 1,703, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Forty Carats to Happy Time.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1980-1997 (Box 1,704, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains The Hasty Heart to Holiday.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1980-2001 (Box 1,705, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Holiday to Les Miserables.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1981-1987 (Box 1,706, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Light Comedies to Little Foxes.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1968-1992 (Box 1,707, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Little Foxes to A Man For All Seasons.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1978-1999 (Box 1,708, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains A Man For All Seasons to Measure For Measure.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1967-1999 (Box 1,709, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Measure For Measure to More Stately Mansions.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1967-1992 (Box 1,710, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains More Stately Mansions to Nicholas Nickleby.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1975-1986 (Box 1,711, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Nicholas Nickleby to On Golden Pond.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1977-1985 (Box 1,712, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains On Golden Pond to Patriot For Me.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1974-1990 (Box 1,713, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Patriot For Me to Pygmalion.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1971-2001 (Box 1,714, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Pygmalion to Sarafina!
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1972-2000 (Box 1,715, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Sarafina! to A Streetcar Named Desire.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1969-2001 (Box 1,716, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains A Streetcar Named Desire to 3hree Lavender Girl.
  - Ahmanson Theatre photographs, 1969-1995 (Box 1,717, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Time of the Cuckoo to The Woman Warrior.
  - Ahmanson Theatre renovation photographs, 1994, 1998 (Box 1,718, Folder 1-4)
    This box also contains A Tribute to Caroline Ahmanson book and Ahmanson Theatre renovation publicity materials.
  - Ahmanson Theatre oversize photographs, 1967-1969 (Box 1,719, Folder 1-23)
  - More Stately Mansions oversize photographs, 1967-1968 (Box 1,720, Folder 1-7)
    This box also contains Ahmanson Theatre resolutions dated 1994 and 2008.
  - Ahmanson Theatre negatives, undated (Box 1,721, Folder 1)
  - Ahmanson Theatre oversize slides, undated (Box 1,722, Folder 1)
    This box contains slides for the following productions: Macbeth, More Stately Mansions, Private Lives, Saint Joan, A Streetcar Named Desire, and Time of the Cuckoo.
  - Ahmanson Theatre window cards, undated (Box 1,723, Folder 1)
  - Ahmanson Theatre at the UCLA James A. Doolittle Theater window cards, undated (Box 1,724, Folder 1)
  - Gordon Davidson VHSs, 1982-2002 (Box 1,725, Folder 1-13)
    This box contains thirteen VHSs and includes the following titles: Stella Adler memorial video, Southland Opera, Law and Order Adam Davidson episode, Sandy Ungar Czech piece, Life and Times Gordon Davidson: Echoes in the Grid, Mark Taper Forum 20th Anniversary Gala Part 1 of 2, Isaac Bashevis Singer The Slave, Master Class news clips, Mark Taper Forum promo tape, The Music Center A Quarter Century of Service, The Music Center 25th Anniversary KCET broadcast, Gordon Davidson Mr. LA Theatre, and Showtime at the Taper rehearsal.
  - Gordon Davidson VHSs, 1986-2001 (Box 1,726, Folder 1-14)
    This box contains fourteen VHS and includes the following titles: CTG Promotional Video, The Mark Taper Forum 20th Anniversary Gala Part 2 of 2, Y.A.P. Jitney, Young Filmmaker Adam Davidson, Bergamot Tour, Robert Fryer, Harold Clurman A LIfe of Theater, Adam Davidson (5 cuts), Clurman: A Life in the Theatre, Stella Adler Memorial Video, Harold Clurman: A Life in the Theatre (rough cut), Mark Taper Forum QED, and Armenia Presentation Video.
  - Gordon Davidson VHSs, 1989-2002 (Box 1,727, Folder 1-7)
    This box contains six VHSs and includes the following titles: 3 Weeks After Paradise, Adam Davidson (5 cuts), American Masters videos, Adam Davidson composite tape, Adam Davidson - Cannes, 3 Weeks After Paradise A Film by Israel Horowitz work cut, and a U-Matic entitled Gordon!
  - Center Theatre Group VHSs, 1991-2007 (Box 1,728, Folder 1-14)
    This box contains fourteen VHSs and includes the following titles: Lobby Video Edward Scissorhands and Black Rider, One Hour Loop Tape Swan Lake, Dame EDNA and Black Rider, One Hour Loop Tape Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf and Edward Scissorhands, Amadeus - Old Vic, Season Lobby Loop, Thoroughly Modern Millie, Esther Wachtell Artists in Residence, Ahmanson Theatre Matthew Bourne's Play Without Words, P.L.A.Y. Performing for Los Angeles Youth, and Swing! at the Ahmanson.
  - Center Theatre Group VHSs, 1975-2010 (Box 1,729, Folder 1-13)
    This box contains two VHSs and includes the following titles: Kevin Kuhlke Splendor Becoming Memories and Minstrel Man. This box contains the following 5 U-Matics: Mark Taper Forum Pirandello 1 and 2 Credits Only, Juno and the Paycock Part 1 and 2, Center Theatre Group Songs in Your Head, and Scenes from Byron - Mad, Bad, and Dangerous to Know Ahmanson Doolittle. This box also contains the following six DVDs: Center Theatre Group Lobby Loop, Ahmanson Theatre Lobby Loop, Center Theatre Group Lobby Video, and Ahmanson Theatre Chorus Line Drowsy Chaperone Lobby Loop.
  - Center Theatre Group U-Matics, 1990-1991 (Box 1,730, Folder 1-4)
    This box contains two U-Matics and includes the following titles: Center Theatre Group Gossip, Clurman Segment, and Center Theatre Group Songs In Your Head. This box also contains a Center Theatre Group Ahmanson Collection stamp.
  - Center Theatre Group 35mm film, 1990-1991 (Box 1,731, Folder 1-6)
    This box contains two 35mm films and includes the following titles: Cocktail Hour and The Vortex.
  - Center Theatre Group 35mm film, 1990-1991 (Box 1,732, Folder 1-7)
    This box contains seven The Vortex 35mm films.
  - Center Theatre Group 35mm film, 1990-1991 (Box 1,733, Folder 1-10)
    This box contains ten The Vortex 35mm films.
  - Center Theatre Group 35mm film, 1990-1991 (Box 1,734, Folder 1-16)
    This box contains sixteen The Vortex 35mm films.
  - Center Theatre Group 35mm film, 1975 (Box 1,735, Folder 1)
    This box contains one 35mm film labeled "Film Realite Tails".
  - Center Theatre Group 16mm film, undated, 1973 (Box 1,736, Folder 1-6)
    This box contains six 16mm films and include the following: Hal Gerson Hadrian VII original silent, Hal Gerson Hadrian VII original sound, Hal Gerson Hadrian VII work print silent, Charlton Heston 1973 season subscription CTG, and New York City Opera.
  - Center Theatre Group 1/4 inch audiotape, 1970-1991 (Box 1,737, Folder 1-14)
    This box contains fourteen 1/4 inch audiotapes and includes the following titles: Gossip, The Vortex, CTG, and Felix De Cola.
  - Center Theatre Group 1/4 inch audiotape, 1969-1991 (Box 1,738, Folder 1-13)